[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":22677,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":33273,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6195,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":39472,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1671,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":41144,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2374,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":43519,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":966,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":44487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4886,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":49376,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2006,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":51383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1760,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":53144,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":914,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":54063,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If th e sum is  6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1662,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":55727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":797,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":56526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1591,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":58119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2- 0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":859,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":58980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1392,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":60375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":846,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":61223,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to  perform  +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1790,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":63015,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":810,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":63827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":1241,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":65070,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1902,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":66975,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1534,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":68510,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":281782,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":350294,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":35644,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":385945,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarl y, 3 is  its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":30363,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":416314,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3653,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":419971,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4275,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":424250,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an el ement is  the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":1752,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":426005,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":695,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":426706,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1214,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":427922,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Co rrect! T he inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":589,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":428513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1055,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":429570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":598,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":430169,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br />  (Remembe r, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2910,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":433082,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5549,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":438633,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":51757,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":490392,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have  one las t definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":38961,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":529358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make e very oth er element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":6069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":535431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":949,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":536382,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2169,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":538553,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generat or under  +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":9347,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":547903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3762,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":551669,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 , and 0  = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1078,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":552749,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":6230,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":558981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1221,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":560204,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1 , 2, 3,  4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":12751,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":572957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5125,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":578084,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":951,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":579036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3 ?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2455,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":581492,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3002,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":584495,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3549,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":588046,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":590476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["1","3"],"rt":2334,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":592811,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5 because 4+1=5 and you do not have to subtract the answer from 9 because 5 is less than 9.","response_history":["5 be","5 b","5 ","5 because 4+1 ","5 because 4+1-","5 because 4+1=5 and you do not have to subtract the answer from 9 because 5 is less than 9."],"rt":30591,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":623403,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answ er.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 because first, 8+4=12, then 12-9=3","response_history":["3 because you ","3 because you","3 because yo","3 because y","3 because first youdo 8","3 because first youdo ","3 because first youdo","3 because first youd","3 because first you 8+","3 because first you 8","3 because first you ","3 because first you","3 because first yo","3 because first y","3 because first ","3 because first, 8+4-","3 because first, 8+4=12 ","3 because first, 8+4=12, then you s","3 because first, 8+4=12, then you 12-","3 because first, 8+4=12, then you 12","3 because first, 8+4=12, then you 1","3 because first, 8+4=12, then you ","3 because first, 8+4=12, then you","3 because first, 8+4=12, then yo","3 because first, 8+4=12, then y","3 because first, 8+4=12, then 12-0","3 because first, 8+4=12, then 12-9=3"],"rt":33090,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":656497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11 -0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 is the identity because you add any number to 0 and you will get that number back.","response_history":["0 because ","0 because","0 becaus","0 becau","0 beca","0 bec","0 be","0 b","0 is the identity bc","0 is the identity because you add any number to 0 and you will get that number back."],"rt":80307,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":736807,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":6715,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":743526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free ","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2438,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":745966,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because when you 3+6 you get 9 then 9-9=0, and inverse of a number is a number you add to get 0.","response_history":["6 because when you 3+6 you get 9 ","6 because when you 3+6 you get 9 then 9-9=0, and inverse of a number is something you ad","6 because when you 3+6 you get 9 then 9-9=0, and inverse of a number is somethin","6 because when you 3+6 you get 9 then 9-9=0, and inverse of a number is somethi","6 because when you 3+6 you get 9 then 9-9=0, and inverse of a number is someth","6 because when you 3+6 you get 9 then 9-9=0, and inverse of a number is somet","6 because when you 3 +6 you g et 9 then 9-9=0, and inverse of a number is some","6 because when you 3+6 you get 9 then 9-9=0, and inverse of a number is som","6 because when you 3+6 you get 9 then 9-9=0, and inverse of a number is so","6 because when you 3+6 you get 9 then 9-9=0, and inverse of a number is s","6 because when you 3+6 you get 9 then 9-9=0, and inverse of a number is a number you add to get 0."],"rt":48732,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":794702,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes because you can +9 multiple twos to get any number","response_history":["yes because you a","yes because you can add","yes because you can ad","yes because you can a","yes because you can +9 multiple twos to get any number from 1 to 9","yes because you can +9 multiple twos to get any number f rom 1 to  ","yes because you can +9 multiple twos to get any number ","yes because you can +9 multiple twos to get any number"],"rt":92137,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":886843,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you cannot get some of the numbers such as 1 and 2 using just 3s.","response_history":["no because you cannot get some of the numbers such as 1 and 2 using just 3s.","no because you cannot get some of the numbers such as 1 and 2 using just 3s","no because you cannot get some of the numbers such as 1 and 2 using just 3","no because you cannot get some of the numbers such as 1 and 2 using just 3s."],"rt":45705,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":932551,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a  generato r under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you cannot get some numbers such as 2 or 3 using just 5s.","response_history":["no bcause ","no bcause","no bcaus","no bcau","no bca","no bc","no because you cannot get some numbers sua","no because you cannot get some numbers such as 2 and 3 ","no because you cannot get some numbers such as 2 and 3","no because you cannot get some numbers such as 2 and ","no because you cannot get some numbers such as 2 and","no because you cannot get some numbers such as 2 an","no because you cannot get some numbers such as 2 a","no because you cannot get some numbers such as 2 or 3 using just 5s."],"rt":40372,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":972927,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you cannot get some numbers such as 1 or 2 using just 6s.","response_history":["no because you cannot gt so","no because you cannot gt s","no because you cannot gt ","no because you cannot gt","no because you cannot g","no because you cannot et","no because you cannot e","no because you cannot get some numbers such as 1 or 2 using just 6s."],"rt":25865,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":998796,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":15142,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1013941,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1","response_history":["n","i","inverse of 1 ","i","n-1"],"rt":21515,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1035461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n-x because inverse is the number that you need to add to x to get n.","response_history":["n-x because inverse is rg","n-x because inverse is r","n-x because inverse is the number that you need to add to x to get n."],"rt":56405,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1091871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which  elements  are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"there is no pattern","response_history":["there is no pattern"],"rt":363641,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1455518,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6546,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1462069,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1466141,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":13925,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1480068,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"True. ","response_history":["fale","false","fals","fal","fa","f","t","True ","False, ","False,","False. ","False.","False","Fals","Fal","Fa","F","True. "],"rt":872149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2352219,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":64609,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2416835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"never because you will not be able to get x from just using multiples of x +_n x","response_history":["never because you will not be ba","never because you will not be b","never because you will not be able to get x from x+X","never beca use you  will not be able to get x from x+","never because you will not be able to get x from x","never because you will not be able to get x from just using x","never because you will not be able to get x from just using multiples of x+)","never because you will not be able to get x from just using multiples of x+_nx","never because you will not be able to get x from just using multiples of x+_n x","never because you will not be able to get x from just using multiples of x +_n x"],"rt":211191,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2628031,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":17675,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2645712,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1802,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2647516,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"29","response_history":["29"],"rt":2236,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2649753,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":3654,"trial_type":"question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2653409,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"calculus","response_history":["calculus"],"rt":10694,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2664105,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3423,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2667530,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":2981,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2670512,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2689,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2673203,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understo od the c oncepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3212,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2676417,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2165,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2678585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2681410,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is /are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4561,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2685976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":3472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2689451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"very hard","response_history":["very hard"],"rt":5395,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2694848,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]